penthouse.com 2017-04-08

# privacy

## LAST UPDATED ON May 2nd, 2016

### Thank you for visiting www.penthouse.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy.

What Our Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy (also, "Policy") covers any personal information that Penthouse Global Digital, Inc.'s ("PGD") family of websites that we own and/or control (the "Site(s)"). This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and changing the "Effective Date" at the top. We may also use alternative methods to alert you to changes to the Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating any of the Site(s) or any portion of the Site(s), you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted.

We may add additional sites from time to time as we expand our offerings and this Policy will govern those new sites when added (and they will become part of (the "Site(s)"). You may be accessing our Site(s) from a computer or mobile phone device (through an iPhone or iPad application, for example) and this Policy governs your use of our Site(s) regardless of the means of access.

You can determine when this Privacy Statement was last revised by referring to the date it was "Last Updated" above.

What Personal Information Is Collected

Depending on how you use our SItes, we may ask you to share personal information with us. _Whether you choose to give PGD information is completely up to you, but keep in mind that if you withhold information, you may not be able to use many of our services or Site(s)._

PGD will ask you for information, including some personal information, if you use one of several services:

Becoming a Registered User of www.penthouse.com.

In order to become a registered user of [www.penthouse.com](http://www.penthouse.com/) or other Site(s), you will need to share some personal information, such as your name and e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to visit the Site(s). But, you will have to register if you want to place orders or make full use of our services. Once you register, you will have an account with PGD and a password to access that account. You may never use another person's account without permission and you may not use anyone else's password. You should keep your registration current and complete. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password. Please also let us know if there is any unauthorized use of your account or password. We recommend that you always log out from your account at the end of a session with us to prevent other people from accessing your account without your permission.

Transactions on the Site(s)

When you make a purchase on [www.penthouse.com](http://www.penthouse.com/) or the Site(s), you have to supply a billing address, phone number, shipping address, and credit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of [www.penthouse.com](http://www.penthouse.com/) or the applicable Site. You can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your credit card number, shipping and billing addresses on your account page. If you change your mind about storing this information, you can amend or delete it by going to the relevant area of your account page and following the instructions. You can access this section using your registration password.

Public Information.

Please note that if you choose to share information about yourself in an open format, such as through a Third Party Site(s) like Facebook or Twitter or in the user-generated content elements of our own Site(s), we consider that information to be public information - and not personal information.

How PGD Protects Your Information

We take reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information we collect from you and about you and to protect you against loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. Any personally identifiable information retained by PGD is stored in a secure manner with limited administrative access.

Despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. For example, we cannot ensure the security of your data during transmission to us or the security of your data on an iPhone (or other telephone device that can use iPhone applications) or on your Twitter® page or on another computer. This reality is true of all Internet or data transmission use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.

How PGD Uses Your Personal Information

PGD collects personal information to make our services available for you to use. We use this information for various purposes, such as fulfilling request for our services. We may also use your information to customize your user experience. Anonymous demographic information is aggregated and shared with advertisers and market researchers.

In the event that another company buys the assets or stock of PGD, your personal information may then belong to another entity.

How to Avoid Receiving Newsletters and Other PGD Materials

We use e-mail addresses and mailing addresses to send out newsletters and other announcements with information about PGD's new products, offers and special features. After you become a registered user of [www.Penthouse.com](http://www.penthouse.com/) or associated Site, you can choose not to receive these announcements by opting-out of delivery. If you receive an e-mail and want to avoid further messages, look at the end of the e-mail for instructions on how to remove yourself from the mailing list.

Who Views Your Personal Information 

PGD may share your personal information with companies or third partiees that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, merchant processing, package delivery, sending postal mail and e-mails, analyzing customer data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, investigating fraudulent activity, conducting customer surveys and/or providing customer service. These companies/third parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not disclose your personally identifiable information for other purposes.

Some personal information is stored on servers owned by other companies. Except as otherwise described below, only PGD has the right to access this information.

We currently share aggregate information about our customers with advertisers and marketing partners. This information does not identify individual users.

Any personal information that you include in your profile will be displayed on our Site(s), so please consider this before submitting any such content. Please don't submit any information that you don't want the whole world to know!

Personal information may be disclosed if required by law.

We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services. We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.

Personal information collected on and/or through the Site(s) is stored and processed in the United States and by using any of the Site(s), you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country to the United States.

Cookies, Pixel Tags and Tracking

PGD wants to give you the best possible experience when you visit our websites. We like to constantly update and improve the features on our Site(s), we like to personalize your browsing and shopping experience and we like to recognize you when you return to www.penthouse.com. We have a variety of ways of doing this.

We collect information about how you use our Site(s) by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. When you visit one of our Site(s), a cookie will be sent to your browser and then stored on your computer's hard drive. We use these cookies to track information about how often you visit our web site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave the site. We also link the visitor ID from your cookie to a user ID in our database to help us analyze web traffic and statistics. Other companies help us with data research and analysis, but they are prohibited from using that data for any other purpose. Cookies also help us improve your shopping experience by, among other things, keeping track of your preferences, recognizing you if you are a registered user, and tracking your order as you use our sites If any of your personal information needs to be accessed during that process, you will have to log in or otherwise authenticate yourself.

We use pixel tags (also called web beacons or "clear" gifs) on our Site(s). They help us analyze what our clients like to do on our Site(s) and the effectiveness of our features and advertising. They can also help us customize your browsing and shopping experience. We may use information collected through pixel tags or tracked links in combination with your personally identifiable information. We may also combine personally identifiable information you provide to PGD with other personal information (such as purchase history and demographic information). We often work with other companies to help us track, collect and analyze this information but they are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose.

PGD also works with advertising partners (like Google and DoubleClick) that use cookies, pixel tags and other tracking technologies to serve advertisements on behalf of their retail clients, including PGD, across the Internet, including to you after you have visited our Site(s). These advertising partners engage in remarketing, online behavioral advertising and ad delivery and reporting. With respect to PGD, these advertising partners may collect anonymous information about your browser as it makes visits to websites across the Internet (including our Site(s)) and your interaction with our advertising and e-mail communications. This anonymous information may also be used to tailor advertising for you and others elsewhere on the Internet. PGD will have access to the information collected by these advertising partners and can then use it in combination with personally identifiable information provided by you to PGD to enhance your experience on our Site(s). We will not share that personally identifiable information with these advertising partners.

No Use for any person under 18

Persons under 18 are not permitted to use the Site(s). We do not knowingly collect information from persons under the age of 18. By using the Site(s), you represent that you are at least 18 years old and also understand that you must be at least 18 years old in order to create any type of account.

Social Commerce and Other Third Parties

We work with trusted third parties, including social network sites like Facebook, and with application developers who specialize in social commerce so we can connect to your social networks. Other social networks we use include Twitter, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram, Vine, Pinterest and Google+. All of these companies operate "Third Party Site(s)". We provide access to our Site(s) by third parties and business partners so we can generate interest in our products among members of your social networks and to allow you to share product interests with friends in your network.

The use of any features made available to you on our Site(s) by a third party may result in information being collected or shared about you by us or by the third party. Information collected or shared through any such third party features is considered "public information" by us because the Third Party Site(s) made it publicly available. If you do not want us to be able to access information about you from Third Party Site(s), you must instruct Third Party Site(s) not to share the information. We cannot control how your data is collected, stored, used or shared by Third Party Site(s) or to whom it is disclosed. Please be sure to review the privacy policies and privacy settings on your social networking sites to make sure you understand the information they are sharing. If you do not want a Third Party Site(s) to share information about you, you must contact that site and determine whether it gives you the opportunity to opt out of sharing such information. PGD is not responsible for how these third parties may use information collected from or about you. However, we do identify any areas on our Site(s) where third parties share information about you.

Web Beacons

PGD may allow certain partners to include web beacons within pages on the Site(s). PGD may also share portions of our log file data, including IP address, with these partners for analytics purposes. In the event your IP address is shared, this information may be used to estimate general location and other technographics (such as connection speed, whether you have visited the Site(s) in a shared location, and type of the device used to visit the Site(s)). These partners aggregate information about our advertising and what you see on the Site(s) and then provide auditing, research and reporting for us and our advertisers.

Questions About This Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the content or practices of our Site(s), you can contact PGD directly at:

privacy@penthouse.com

or

Penthouse Global Media Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
8944 Mason Avenue  
Chatsworth, CA 91311  

Our Location

PGD and its servers are located in the United States. If you are visiting any of the Site(s) from outside the United States, your personal information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States or other countries in which our service providers are located. The data protection and other laws of the United States and these other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, and your personal information may be accessible to law enforcement authorities in the United States or of other countries. When you use the Site(s), you consent to us transferring your personal information (which includes, for the avoidance of doubt, your sensitive personal information) from your country to the United States or countries in which PGD or its service providers are located for the purposes described in this Policy. PGD does not warrant or represent that it complies with the laws regarding the collection, holding, or processing of personal data in your country.  If you do not accept this term or other terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or any PGD related website, products, or services.

Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by PGD to its affiliates and/or third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

To make such a request, please send an email with your first name, last name, mailing address, email address and telephone number to support@penthouse.com. Please include "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line of your email.

You may also make such a request by writing to us at:

Penthouse Global Digital, Inc.  
Attn: California Privacy Rights  
8944 Mason Avenue  
Chatsworth, CA 91311  

Third Party Site(s)

We also like to interact with you on third party sites where we post content or invite your feedback (such as Twitter, Facebook and YouTube, etc. also known as "Third Party Site(s)" as referred to above):

Except as otherwise noted above, this Policy does not cover the privacy practices of those Third Party Site(s), or of companies that PGD does not own or control, or the actions of people that PGD does not employ or manage. You should check the privacy policies of those third parties when providing personally identifiable information through Third Party Site(s). Our terms of use for the Site(s) also gives you more information about how we can interact with you via Third Party Site(s).
